levo.com 2017-06-20

# Privacy Policy - Levo

The Levo League Corporation is committed to maintaining robust privacy protections for its users. Our Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Site or our Service. For purposes of this Agreement, "Site" refers to www.levoleague.com and "Service" refers to our service designed to provide content and services targeting Generation Y women. The terms "Levo League," "we," "us," and "our" refer to The Levo League Corporation, a Delaware limited liability corporation. "You" refers to you, as a user of the Site or the Service. By accepting our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use (found here: www.levoleague.com/terms) ("Terms of Use"), you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. Any terms we use in this Privacy Policy without defining them have the definitions given to them in the Terms of Use.

  1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT
  2. HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION
  3. HOW WE STORE AND PROTECT INFORMATION
  4. YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING THE USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
  5. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
  6. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
  7. CONTACT US

## I. INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect "Non-Personal Information" and "Personal Information." Non-Personal Information includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as anonymous usage data, general demographic information we may collect, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you submit and number of clicks. Personal Information includes your email and other information which you submit to us through the registration process at the Site or that you provide to Recruiters or Employers via use of our Site, such as your resume and personal contact information. 

### Information collected via Technology

To access and use elements of the Service, and to post your resume on the Site or provide your resume to Recruiters and Employers via our site, you will likely need to submit Personal Information. Also, in an effort to improve the quality of the Site and the Service, we track information provided to us by your browser when you view the Site or use the Service, such as the website you came from (known as the "referring URL"), the type of browser you use, the device from which you connected to the Service, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you. We may track this information using cookies, or small text files which include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to a user's browser from our servers and are stored on the user's computer hard drive. Sending a cookie to a user's browser enables us to collect Non-Personal information about that user and keep a record of the user's preferences when utilizing our services, both on an individual and aggregate basis. 

Levo League may use both persistent and session cookies; persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your session and until you delete them, while session cookies expire when you close your browser. 

### Information you provide us by using the Service

In addition to the information provided automatically by your browser when you visit the Site, to use elements of the Service you will need to create a personal profile or purchase certain products or services. You can create a profile by registering directly through the Site and uploading your resume, a photograph, your email address and other contact information, and creating a user name and a password. If you purchase products or services, then we or our third party payment processor will also ask for additional information, such as your credit card number and billing address. We may also retain any messages you send through the Service. By registering or purchasing products or services, you are authorizing us to collect, store and use your email address and other Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### Minors

Levo League does not knowingly collect or solicit information from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 18, please do not attempt to register for Levo League or send any information about you to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 18 may provide any information to or on Levo League. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a child under 13 may have provided us personal information, please contact us at info@levo.com.

## II. HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION

### Personal Information

We use your Personal Information to operate, maintain, improve, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service. Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise share for marketing purposes your Personal Information with third parties without your consent. We do share Personal Information with vendors who are performing services for Levo League, such as the servers for our email communications who are provided access to user's email address for purposes of sending emails from us. Our vendors use your Personal Information only at our direction and in accordance with our Privacy Policy. We also use third party payment processors to collect and store your payment card information and to process payments in connection with the Service. Any information that you provide to our payment processors is governed by each processor’s separate privacy policy instead of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties. Levo League neither collects nor stores your payment card information on its servers. 

In general, the Personal Information you provide to us is used to help us communicate with you. For example, we use Personal Information to contact users in response to questions, solicit feedback from users, provide technical support, and inform users about promotional offers. 

We also permit you to designate Recruiters and Employers on our Site with whom you wish to share your Personal Information and that Personal Information is shared with the Recruiters and Employers you designate as part of our Service. How such Recruiters and Employers use your information once you have submitted that information to them Levo League cannot control and you acknowledge and agree that Levo League has no responsibility our your Personal Information is used by the Recruiters and Employers you designate or you submit your Personal Information to. Recruiters will likely use your Personal Information to contact you and to consider you for employment; provided that submission of your Personal Information does not create any expectation or guarantee that any Recruiter and Employer will employ you based on your submission of Personal Information via our Site or our Service. 

### Non-Personal Information

In general, we use Non-Personal Information to help us operate, maintain, improve, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service and to customize the user experience. We also may aggregate Non-Personal Information in order to track trends and analyze use patterns on the Site. This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of Non-Personal Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Non-Personal Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our discretion and for any purpose, including research and marketing purposes. 

In the event we undergo a business transaction such as a merger, reorganization, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information and Non- Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of our assets may continue to process your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at any time in the future, we will post the policy changes to the Site so that you may opt out of the new information practices. We suggest that you check the Site periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used. 

## III. HOW WE STORE AND PROTECT INFORMATION

Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Levo League or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. Levo League may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which Levo League or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy. 

We implement security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. Your account is protected by your account password and we urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe by not disclosing your password and by logging out of your account after each use. We further protect your information from potential security breaches by implementing certain technological security measures including encryption, firewalls and secure socket layer technology. However, these measures do not guarantee that your information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. By using our Service, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks. 

## IV. YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING THE USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You have the right at any time to prevent us from contacting you for marketing purposes. When we send a promotional communication to a user, the user can opt out of further promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in each promotional e-mail. You can also indicate that you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us in the "Settings" section of the Site. Please note that notwithstanding the promotional preferences you indicate by either unsubscribing or opting out in the Settings section of the Site, we may continue to send you administrative emails including, for example, periodic updates to our Privacy Policy. 

## V. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

As part of the Service, we may provide links to or compatibility with other websites or content, including the websites of Recruiters and Employers for job opportunities listed on our Site. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those websites, the information or content they contain, or the privacy practices of the Recruiters and Employers listed on our Site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site and the Service and not to any submissions once made to Recruiters and Employers. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of other websites before proceeding to use them. 

## VI. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Levo League reserves the right to change this policy and our Terms of Service at any time. We will notify you of significant changes to our Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. Significant changes will go into effect 30 days following such notification. Non-material changes or clarifications will take effect immediately. You should periodically check the Site and this privacy page for updates. If you do not agree with the terms of the new Privacy Policy, you are free to reject them; unfortunately, that means you will no longer be able to access or use the Site or Service. Your access or use of the Site or Service in any way after a change to this Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of the new Privacy Policy. 

## VII. CONTACT US

Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of information which we share with our affiliates or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to: info@levo.com or the postal mail address located below. 

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please contact us by sending an email to [info@levo.com](mailto:info@levo.com) or by contacting us at the postal address below. 

The Levo League Corporation  
1 Union Square West, 701  
New York, NY 10003  

Last Updated: This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 16, 2016.
